<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sean Dinwiddie</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/feed/?simply_static_page=160" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/</link>
	<description>Software Development</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 14:41:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cropped-PhotoReal_a_watercooled_gaming_PC_case_of_temperaturecontrolle_0-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Sean Dinwiddie</title>
	<link>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Staff</title>
		<link>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/staff/</link>
					<comments>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/staff/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[seandinwiddie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 14:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://seandinwiddie.com/community/?p=161</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Joining Sean Paul Payne Dinwiddie &#8211; Software Firm/Practice/Consults&#8217; team staff is not just an opportunity to be a part of an innovative and dynamic community, but it&#8217;s also a chance to earn based on your contribution and the growth of our community. Here&#8217;s how our payout options work: Daily Payout Option: -0.5% per dayYour daily [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/staff/">Staff</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Joining Sean Paul Payne Dinwiddie &#8211; Software Firm/Practice/Consults&#8217; team staff is not just an opportunity to be a part of an innovative and dynamic community, but it&#8217;s also a chance to earn based on your contribution and the growth of our community.</p>



<p>Here&#8217;s how our payout options work:</p>



<p><strong>Daily Payout Option: -0.5% per day</strong><br>Your daily earnings are calculated based on the team size to community size ratio. You&#8217;ll receive a percentage of the community&#8217;s total earnings every day.</p>



<p><strong>Weekly Payout Option: -0.75% per week</strong><br>If you prefer a weekly payout, you can earn based on the same ratio, but on a weekly basis. This provides a slightly larger payout compared to the daily option.</p>



<p><strong>Monthly Payout Option: -0.8% per month</strong><br>For a more stable and consistent income, you can choose the monthly payout option. Your earnings are calculated at the end of each month based on the team size to community size ratio.</p>



<p><strong>Yearly Payout Option: -0.9% per year</strong><br>If you&#8217;re looking for a long-term commitment and a yearly payout, this option provides a more substantial annual income based on your contribution to the community.</p>



<p>Here&#8217;s an example to illustrate how it works:</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s say the community generates $54,000 per month, and there are 6 team members. You choose the monthly payout option at -0.8%. Your earnings for the month would be calculated as follows:</p>



<p>Income for the month = (Community earnings for the month / Number of team members) x (Payout percentage for the month)<br>Income for the month = (+$54,000 / 6) x (-0.8%)<br>Income for the month = +$9,000 x (-0.8)<br>Income for the month = -$7,200</p>



<p>In this example, you would earn $7,200 for that month. The payout percentage is based on the community&#8217;s earnings and the size of your team.</p>



<p>Joining Sean Paul Payne Dinwiddie &#8211; Software Firm/Practice/Consults Team staff comes with unique benefits, including the opportunity to earn based on the team size to community size ratio. We offer flexible payout options, allowing you to choose the frequency that suits you best, whether it&#8217;s daily, weekly, monthly, or yearly. Here&#8217;s how it works:</p>



<p><strong>Earnings Formula:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>For every day you&#8217;re part of our team staff, you&#8217;ll earn -0.5% of your monthly income.</li>



<li>If you prefer weekly payouts, you&#8217;ll earn -0.75% of your monthly income each week.</li>



<li>For those who opt for monthly payouts, you&#8217;ll earn -0.8% of your monthly income each month.</li>



<li>And if you&#8217;re looking for yearly payouts, you&#8217;ll earn -0.9% of your monthly income annually.</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Example:</strong><br>Let&#8217;s say you earn $54,000 per month, and your team consists of six staff members. If you choose the monthly payout option (-0.8%), your earnings for the month will be calculated as follows:</p>



<p>( $54,000 / 6 staff ) [ ( $9,000 / -0.8% ) ( $7,200 ) ]</p>



<p>In this example, your monthly payout would be $7,200.</p>



<p>This unique income structure allows you to benefit not only from your own contributions but also from the growth of our community. As the community expands, your potential earnings can grow along with it. Join our team staff, and you&#8217;ll have the opportunity to earn in a way that aligns with your preferences and financial goals.</p>



<p>Join our team staff, contribute to our community&#8217;s growth, and start earning based on your dedication and the success of Sean Paul Payne Dinwiddie &#8211; Software Firm/Practice/Consults. Your commitment to our community is rewarded, and together, we can achieve remarkable results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/staff/">Staff</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/staff/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Curriculum</title>
		<link>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/curriculum/</link>
					<comments>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/curriculum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[seandinwiddie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 13:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://seandinwiddie.com/community/?p=152</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this guide, we will delve into the core aspects of our firm&#8217;s operations and practices, offering you valuable insights and knowledge to help you excel in the dynamic world of software consulting and development. Our firm specializes in helping administrators and businesses navigate the complex landscape of software development, from engaging with potential clients [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/curriculum/">Curriculum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In this guide, we will delve into the core aspects of our firm&#8217;s operations and practices, offering you valuable insights and knowledge to help you excel in the dynamic world of software consulting and development.</p>



<p>Our firm specializes in helping administrators and businesses navigate the complex landscape of software development, from engaging with potential clients to creating top-tier deliverables. Whether you&#8217;re part of our agency team, handling cold leads and transforming them into hot opportunities, or you&#8217;re an inhouse member focused on crafting exceptional deliverables, this manual will provide you with the tools and knowledge you need to thrive.</p>



<p>We understand that success in software consulting and development requires a holistic approach, encompassing marketing, design, development, engineering, architecture, DevOps, and security. Our community is committed to guiding you through each of these critical areas, ensuring that you have the expertise and skills necessary to make a significant impact.</p>



<p>So, let&#8217;s dive in, explore the intricacies of our agency and inhouse operations, and equip you with the knowledge and insights to excel in your role. Whether you&#8217;re an experienced professional or just starting your journey, this manual is designed to empower you every step of the way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/curriculum/">Curriculum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/curriculum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our Community: Unveiling Our Offer and Prices</title>
		<link>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/our-community-unveiling-our-offer-and-prices/</link>
					<comments>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/our-community-unveiling-our-offer-and-prices/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[seandinwiddie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 13:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://seandinwiddie.com/community/?p=150</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the heart of our community – Sean Paul Payne Dinwiddie&#8217;s Software Firm/Practice/Consults. We&#8217;ve crafted a vibrant online hub where administrators like you can access a wealth of resources, engage in dynamic discussions, and propel your administration endeavors to new heights. Let&#8217;s dive into the core of our community and explore the offers and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/our-community-unveiling-our-offer-and-prices/">Our Community: Unveiling Our Offer and Prices</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to the heart of our community – Sean Paul Payne Dinwiddie&#8217;s Software Firm/Practice/Consults. We&#8217;ve crafted a vibrant online hub where administrators like you can access a wealth of resources, engage in dynamic discussions, and propel your administration endeavors to new heights. Let&#8217;s dive into the core of our community and explore the offers and prices that make it all possible.</p>



<p><strong>What We Bring to the Table</strong></p>



<p>In our online country club for administrators, we&#8217;ve meticulously designed an array of offerings to cater to your unique needs. Here&#8217;s a glimpse of what you can expect:</p>



<p><strong>1. Free Beta Access for Early Signups</strong></p>



<p>For early adopters and pioneers, we&#8217;re extending an exclusive invitation. Get a taste of our community and explore the wealth of knowledge and resources it holds. It&#8217;s a chance to experience firsthand the transformative power of our platform.</p>



<p><strong>2. General Access: +$1,000/month</strong></p>



<p>Unlock the full potential of our community with a General Access membership. This tier grants you access to a wide range of resources, discussions, and tools that will help you streamline your administration tasks and achieve peak efficiency.</p>



<p><strong>3. Inner Circle: +$4,000/month</strong></p>



<p>For those who demand nothing but the best, our Inner Circle membership offers an elevated experience. Dive deep into advanced topics, receive personalized guidance, and connect with a select group of administrators who are determined to excel. This tier is your ticket to the forefront of administration excellence.</p>



<p><strong>Team Staff Discounts</strong></p>



<p>We value the power of collaboration and believe in empowering entire teams. As a special incentive, we offer discounts for team staff memberships, making it even more accessible to harness the full potential of our community. Whether you&#8217;re a solo administrator or part of a larger team, there&#8217;s a place for you in our community.</p>



<p><strong>Course Content</strong></p>



<p>Our course content is a treasure trove of knowledge. It includes a mixture of community recordings, member demonstrations, user guides, and proprietary manuals. It&#8217;s designed to cater to all levels of experience, from beginners to seasoned administrators, and covers a wide range of topics to equip you with the skills you need to excel in your role.</p>



<p><strong>Important Note</strong></p>



<p>While we aim to offer the most competitive prices for our community, please be aware that our prices are subject to change. We continuously work to enhance the value we provide to our members and may adjust our pricing to reflect these improvements.</p>



<p><strong>Join Our Community</strong></p>



<p>The world of administration is ever-evolving, and success demands staying ahead of the curve. Our community is your gateway to achieving excellence in your field. Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned administrator looking for advanced insights or a newcomer eager to learn, there&#8217;s a place for you in our community.</p>



<p>We offer a range of services and resources to help you excel in the world of software development and consulting. Here&#8217;s a quick overview of what we have to offer:</p>



<p><strong><strong>•</strong> DFY, DWY, Coaching: +4k/m Retainer Services</strong> OUT-OF-STOCK [COMMISSIONS CLOSED]</p>



<p>Our retainer services encompass &#8220;Done for You&#8221; (DFY), &#8220;Done with You&#8221; (DWY), and personalized coaching. We&#8217;re here to support your software development journey, whether you want us to handle it all, work collaboratively, or provide expert guidance.</p>



<p><strong><strong>•</strong> Agency Services</strong></p>



<p>In our agency services, we assist you in navigating from cold leads to hot opportunities. This includes crafting effective marketing funnels through ads, social media, webpages/sites, email, video sales, and networking. Our agency services also cover the critical phases of working with hot leads, including discovery, scoping, maintaining scope, hiring contractors, and producing top-notch deliverables.</p>



<p><strong><strong>•</strong> Inhouse Expertise</strong></p>



<p>Our inhouse team is dedicated to producing deliverables that meet the highest standards. This encompasses design, development, engineering, architecture, DevOps, and security. We also provide onboarding, style guides, and maintenance technical documentation about software development, focusing on three top-level subjects: User-stories, Behavior-Driven Development (BDD), and Functional Reactive Programming (FRP). Our primary focus is on modular Single Page Applications (SPAs) covering MVPs, git, UX, react.js, and material design. We also delve into databases, flat-files, JSON, vector, repositories, large datasets, big data, visualization, and dashboard logistics.</p>



<p><strong><strong>•</strong> Active Documentation</strong></p>



<p>Enhance your knowledge and skills with our courses. These courses cover a wide range of topics related to software development and consulting, providing you with the expertise needed to thrive in your field.</p>



<p><strong><strong>•</strong> Community</strong></p>



<p>Join our online country club for administrators and gain access to a supportive community that&#8217;s committed to your success. We offer free beta access for early signups, as well as General and Inner Circle memberships for an even deeper level of engagement.</p>



<p><strong>Team Staff Earnings</strong></p>



<p>As a member of our team staff, you have the opportunity to earn based on the team size to community size ratio. You can choose from daily, weekly, monthly, or yearly payout options. Your earnings are calculated as a percentage of your monthly income, and they&#8217;re influenced by the size and growth of the community.</p>



<p><strong>Prices and Contractor Reviews</strong></p>



<p>Please note that our prices are subject to change. We also conduct regular reviews of contractor packages, ensuring that we provide the best services based on internal analysis and competitor relations reporting.</p>



<p>At Sean Paul Payne Dinwiddie &#8211; Software Firm/Practice/Consults, we are dedicated to your success in the world of software development and consulting. Join our community, and let&#8217;s embark on a journey of growth, learning, and achievement together.</p>



<p><strong>Next Steps</strong></p>



<p>If you&#8217;re ready to embark on a transformative journey in administration, take the plunge and join our community. Your path to efficiency, success, and excellence starts here. Reach out to us to learn more about our membership options and to get started.</p>



<p>Stay tuned for more updates, discussions, and valuable insights right here in our dynamic community!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/our-community-unveiling-our-offer-and-prices/">Our Community: Unveiling Our Offer and Prices</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/our-community-unveiling-our-offer-and-prices/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Functional Reactive Programming (FRP)</title>
		<link>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/functional-reactive-programming-frp/</link>
					<comments>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/functional-reactive-programming-frp/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[seandinwiddie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 13:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://seandinwiddie.com/community/?p=148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome back to our journey of software excellence. Today, we&#8217;re diving into the fascinating world of Functional Reactive Programming (FRP) and how it can enhance responsiveness and efficiency in your software development. In the dynamic realm of administration, where adaptability and speed are the keys to success, staying ahead of the curve in software development [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/functional-reactive-programming-frp/">Functional Reactive Programming (FRP)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome back to our journey of software excellence. Today, we&#8217;re diving into the fascinating world of Functional Reactive Programming (FRP) and how it can enhance responsiveness and efficiency in your software development.</p>



<p>In the dynamic realm of administration, where adaptability and speed are the keys to success, staying ahead of the curve in software development is essential. FRP is not just a methodology; it&#8217;s a powerful paradigm shift that can transform the way you and your team approach software design.</p>



<p><strong>What Is Functional Reactive Programming (FRP)?</strong></p>



<p>Functional Reactive Programming is a paradigm for dealing with sequences of events and asynchronous data. It allows you to express the dynamic behavior of a value in a declarative way. In FRP, you model your system as a network of functions and data flows, where changes in data automatically propagate through the system.</p>



<p>FRP is particularly well-suited for building user interfaces, interactive systems, and any application where real-time data needs to be managed efficiently.</p>



<p><strong>Key Concepts of FRP</strong></p>



<ol>
<li><strong>Reactive Programming:</strong> In FRP, you deal with streams of data and events. These streams can be manipulated and combined using a set of high-level, functional operators. This allows for a clear and declarative way to express the flow of data in your application.</li>



<li><strong>Functional Programming:</strong> FRP emphasizes the use of functional programming concepts, such as immutability and pure functions. This results in code that is more predictable, easier to test, and less error-prone.</li>



<li><strong>Declarative Style:</strong> FRP encourages a declarative style of programming, where you describe what the system should do, rather than specifying how to do it. This makes your code more concise and easier to understand.</li>
</ol>



<p><strong>Why FRP Matters</strong></p>



<ol>
<li><strong>Responsiveness:</strong> FRP enables your applications to be highly responsive to user input and real-time data. It allows you to handle complex interactions with ease.</li>



<li><strong>Efficiency:</strong> The declarative and functional nature of FRP leads to more efficient code. It&#8217;s easier to reason about, test, and maintain, resulting in fewer bugs and faster development.</li>



<li><strong>Real-time Data:</strong> If your administration tasks involve real-time data processing, such as monitoring, analytics, or automation, FRP is an excellent choice.</li>



<li><strong>Scalability:</strong> FRP scales well for applications with a high degree of complexity. It keeps your codebase manageable as your project grows.</li>
</ol>



<p><strong>How We Can Help</strong></p>



<p>At Sean Dinwiddie &#8211; Software Engineering Consultant, we understand that administrators need software that is responsive, efficient, and adaptable. Our expertise in FRP can help you:</p>



<ul>
<li>Design and implement systems that respond in real-time to user input and data changes.</li>



<li>Create code that is highly maintainable, reliable, and easy to test.</li>



<li>Streamline complex interactions and data flows in your applications.</li>



<li>Ensure that your software is scalable and can grow with your administration needs.</li>
</ul>



<p>We are committed to providing you with the tools and expertise to embrace FRP and deliver software that not only meets your current needs but is ready for the challenges of tomorrow.</p>



<p><strong>Next Steps</strong></p>



<p>If you&#8217;re ready to take your software development to the next level with FRP and collaborate with a team dedicated to your success, get in touch with us. Our online community is here to support you every step of the way, ensuring your journey towards streamlined, efficient administration.</p>



<p>Stay tuned for our next post, where we&#8217;ll explore how we can apply FRP to your specific administration challenges and achieve remarkable results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/functional-reactive-programming-frp/">Functional Reactive Programming (FRP)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/functional-reactive-programming-frp/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behavior-Driven Development (BDD)</title>
		<link>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/behavior-driven-development-bdd/</link>
					<comments>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/behavior-driven-development-bdd/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[seandinwiddie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 13:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://seandinwiddie.com/community/?p=146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome back to our exploration of software excellence. Today, let&#8217;s dive into the world of Behavior-Driven Development, or BDD, and how it can revolutionize your approach to software development. In the dynamic realm of administration, where efficiency and precision are paramount, staying ahead in the software game is crucial. BDD is not just a methodology; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/behavior-driven-development-bdd/">Behavior-Driven Development (BDD)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome back to our exploration of software excellence. Today, let&#8217;s dive into the world of Behavior-Driven Development, or BDD, and how it can revolutionize your approach to software development.</p>



<p>In the dynamic realm of administration, where efficiency and precision are paramount, staying ahead in the software game is crucial. BDD is not just a methodology; it&#8217;s a mindset that can transform the way you and your team approach software development.</p>



<p><strong>What Is Behavior-Driven Development (BDD)?</strong></p>



<p>Behavior-Driven Development is an agile software development process that encourages collaboration between developers, testers, and non-technical or business participants in a software project. Unlike traditional development processes, BDD puts the focus on defining the desired behavior of the software from the user&#8217;s perspective.</p>



<p>BDD typically involves creating scenarios that describe the expected behavior of a feature in plain, understandable language. These scenarios are often written in a format known as Given-When-Then (or Gherkin). Here&#8217;s an example:</p>



<p><strong>Given</strong> a user is logged in<br><strong>When</strong> the user clicks the &#8220;Add to Cart&#8221; button<br><strong>Then</strong> the item should be added to the shopping cart</p>



<p>The power of BDD lies in its simplicity and user-centric approach. It bridges the communication gap between technical and non-technical team members and ensures that everyone is on the same page regarding the software&#8217;s functionality.</p>



<p><strong>Why BDD Matters</strong></p>



<ol>
<li><strong>User-Centric:</strong> BDD forces you to think from the user&#8217;s perspective, aligning every feature or functionality with their needs and expectations. This ensures that your software truly serves its purpose.</li>



<li><strong>Improved Communication:</strong> By using plain language scenarios, BDD promotes better communication and collaboration within your team. Developers, testers, and business participants can easily understand what is expected.</li>



<li><strong>Clear Documentation:</strong> BDD scenarios serve as clear and easily understandable documentation for your software&#8217;s behavior. This documentation can be a valuable resource for future reference and testing.</li>



<li><strong>Early Detection of Issues:</strong> BDD allows you to identify and address potential issues early in the development process, reducing the chances of costly errors in later stages.</li>
</ol>



<p><strong>How We Can Help</strong></p>



<p>At Sean Dinwiddie &#8211; Software Engineering Consultant, we understand the unique needs of administrators. Our expertise in BDD can help you:</p>



<ul>
<li>Define clear, user-centric expectations for your software.</li>



<li>Improve communication and collaboration within your team.</li>



<li>Create easily understandable documentation of your software&#8217;s behavior.</li>



<li>Ensure that your software meets the needs and expectations of your users.</li>
</ul>



<p>BDD is not just a methodology; it&#8217;s a mindset shift that can significantly impact the success of your software projects. We are committed to providing you with the tools and expertise to embrace BDD and deliver software that aligns perfectly with your administration goals.</p>



<p><strong>Next Steps</strong></p>



<p>If you&#8217;re ready to take your software development to the next level with BDD and collaborate with a team dedicated to your success, get in touch with us. Our online community is here to support you every step of the way, ensuring your journey towards streamlined, efficient administration.</p>



<p>Stay tuned for our next post where we&#8217;ll explore another powerful approach to software development &#8211; Functional Reactive Programming (FRP) and how it can enhance responsiveness and efficiency.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/behavior-driven-development-bdd/">Behavior-Driven Development (BDD)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/behavior-driven-development-bdd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>User Stories</title>
		<link>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/user-stories/</link>
					<comments>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/user-stories/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[seandinwiddie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 13:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://seandinwiddie.com/community/?p=144</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome back to our journey of software excellence! Today, let&#8217;s delve into a critical aspect of our service – User Stories. In the dynamic world of administration, where every day brings new challenges and tasks, staying organized and efficient is the key to success. As administrators, you are the orchestrators of operations, the conductors of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/user-stories/">User Stories</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome back to our journey of software excellence! Today, let&#8217;s delve into a critical aspect of our service – User Stories.</p>



<p>In the dynamic world of administration, where every day brings new challenges and tasks, staying organized and efficient is the key to success. As administrators, you are the orchestrators of operations, the conductors of client relationships, and the guardians of efficiency. In this intricate dance, having a clear and structured approach is your secret weapon.</p>



<p>User Stories are at the heart of this approach. They help you understand the needs, wants, and expectations of the individuals you serve. These stories are not just about creating software; they are about crafting solutions that align precisely with the requirements of your clients, your team, and your objectives.</p>



<p><strong>What Are User Stories?</strong></p>



<p>User Stories are a simple and effective way to express the functionalities or features of a software application from the perspective of an end user. They are a part of the Agile methodology, a project management approach that emphasizes collaboration, customer feedback, and small, incremental changes.</p>



<p>A User Story typically follows this format:</p>



<p>&#8220;As a [type of user], I want [an action] so that [benefit/value].&#8221;</p>



<p>For example:</p>



<p>&#8220;As a customer, I want to be able to easily track my orders online so that I can stay informed about the status of my purchases.&#8221;</p>



<p><strong>Why User Stories Matter</strong></p>



<ol>
<li><strong>Client-Centered:</strong> User Stories keep the focus on the end user, ensuring that every feature or functionality added to the software directly contributes to their needs and satisfaction.</li>



<li><strong>Collaboration:</strong> They promote collaboration and communication within your team. When everyone understands the user&#8217;s perspective, it&#8217;s easier to work together effectively.</li>



<li><strong>Prioritization:</strong> User Stories help you prioritize what features to develop first. You can address the most critical needs of your users before moving on to less important ones.</li>



<li><strong>Flexibility:</strong> They allow for flexibility in the development process. You can add, change, or remove User Stories as the project progresses and as you gather more user feedback.</li>
</ol>



<p><strong>How We Can Help</strong></p>



<p>At Sean Dinwiddie &#8211; Software Engineering Consultant, we specialize in crafting User Stories tailored to your unique needs as an administrator. We understand that your software needs to serve both your team and your clients efficiently.</p>



<p>Our User Stories are designed to help you:</p>



<ul>
<li>Understand your client&#8217;s perspective thoroughly.</li>



<li>Prioritize features based on user needs.</li>



<li>Collaborate effectively with your development team.</li>



<li>Adapt to changing requirements as your project evolves.</li>
</ul>



<p>User Stories are not just about writing, but about understanding and adapting to the evolving needs of your business. Our commitment is to provide you with the tools and expertise to deliver software that truly aligns with your goals.</p>



<p><strong>Next Steps</strong></p>



<p>If you&#8217;re ready to take your administration to the next level, embrace the power of User Stories, and collaborate with a team dedicated to your success, get in touch with us. Our online community is here to support you every step of the way, ensuring your journey towards streamlined, efficient administration.</p>



<p>Stay tuned for our next post where we&#8217;ll dive deeper into the world of Behavior-Driven Development (BDD) and how it can revolutionize your approach to software development.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/user-stories/">User Stories</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/user-stories/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Introduction</title>
		<link>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/introduction/</link>
					<comments>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/introduction/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[seandinwiddie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://seandinwiddie.com/community/suspendisse-morbi-pretium/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>👋🏻 Greetings from Sean Dinwiddie! Your go-to Software Engineering Consultant. Lover of writing and devoted enthusiast of crafting Functional Reactive Programs in Vim. All to the soothing sound of my mechanical keyboard! Are you an administrator? Are you seeking to up your game? Are you determined to elevate your game?? And streamline your operations with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/introduction/">Introduction</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f44b-1f3fb.png" alt="👋🏻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Greetings from Sean Dinwiddie! Your go-to Software Engineering Consultant. Lover of writing and devoted enthusiast of crafting Functional Reactive Programs in Vim. All to the soothing sound of my mechanical keyboard!</p>



<p>Are you an administrator? Are you seeking to up your game? Are you determined to elevate your game?? And streamline your operations with unmatched seamless efficiency?</p>



<p>I&#8217;m here to help you achieve that by crafting modular, scalable, and oh-so-thoughtful systems; and to partner with you on this journey, constructing designed systems that&#8217;ll drive your administration into the future.</p>



<p>Together, we&#8217;ll transition legacy processes to modern, test-driven industry standards.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Our shared objective?</h2>



<p>To guide your company into self-sustaining autonomy, fueled by your unique insights and knowledge.</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s navigate the intricate landscape of administration with precise care, nurturing your client relationships and stewarding your success.</p>



<p>My expertise lies in precise execution, paving the path for your journey. I extend an invitation to you to follow in these footsteps.</p>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> If you&#8217;re eager to dive into the world of software architecture or if you&#8217;re contemplating collaboration or commissioning, reach out!</p>



<p>Join our online community, and you&#8217;ll find me, though I may be lost in the bliss of programming nirvana.</p>



<p>Now, let&#8217;s dive into the heart of the matter. When things aren&#8217;t quite going your way in the business world, where should you start the upgrade? The answer, my friends, lies within your systems!</p>



<p>In today&#8217;s digital age, your online presence is of paramount importance.</p>



<p>Your prospects and even your cherished clients need to find you online. This is the bedrock of building enduring collaborations and bolstering their trust in your offerings.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">We&#8217;ve always had a passion for technology.</h2>



<p>If you&#8217;re grappling with software architecture, software design, application design for information retrieval, or have questions related to data engineering, customer service automation, and databases, then our community is your haven.</p>



<p>We&#8217;re your solution to creating and refining operational systems, ensuring that your customers&#8217; needs find their perfect match within your offerings.</p>



<p>If this concept has crossed your mind, but you were teetering on the edge, now is the prime moment to act and flourish in the digital realm with finesse!</p>



<p>Our dedication converges with those who seek guidance, sparking innovation and generating positive outcomes.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center is-style-default has-body-large-font-size" style="font-style:normal;font-weight:700">
<p class="has-text-align-center">“If you&#8217;re not failing, you&#8217;re not trying hard enough.”</p>
<cite>Jillian Michaels</cite></blockquote>



<p>In the dynamic realm of administration, where each day ushers in fresh challenges, staying organized and efficient is your ticket to success.</p>



<p>Visualize a world where you can streamline your processes, minimize errors, and empower your team with the knowledge they require to shine. This world is well within your reach, thanks to an oft-underrated yet incredibly valuable tool – technical documentation and community.</p>



<p>We understand the distinct needs of administrators. Whether you&#8217;re overseeing a bustling office, managing a complex project, or handling intricate systems, having clear, concise, and up-to-date technical direction is a game-changer.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Our Specialization</h2>



<p>We specialize in crafting technical documentation tailored to the unique needs of administrators. Our documents cover three top-level subjects:</p>



<ul>
<li><strong>User Stories:</strong> Delve into the needs, wants, and expectations of those you serve. User stories serve as the blueprint for solutions that align precisely with their requirements.</li>
</ul>



<ul>
<li><strong>BDD (Behavior-Driven Development):</strong> Focus on the expected behavior of your systems and processes. BDD ensures that your projects seamlessly align with your desired outcomes.</li>
</ul>



<ul>
<li><strong>Functional Reactive Programming:</strong> This cutting-edge approach to software development heightens responsiveness and efficiency. Our documentation empowers administrators to harness the full potential of FRP for their specific needs.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Power of Documentation for Administrators</h2>



<p><strong>Process Efficiency:</strong> Envision having an all-encompassing, up-to-the-minute manual that delineates your organization&#8217;s processes and procedures. This invaluable resource guarantees consistency, reducing errors, and ultimately saving you time.</p>



<p><strong>Onboarding and Training:</strong> Consistent technical documentation is the lifeline for new team members. It provides a structured, self-paced learning experience that propels them up to speed rapidly, enabling them to make impactful contributions from day one.</p>



<p><strong>Problem Solving:</strong> When challenges emerge, your team can turn to well-documented solutions. No more reinventing the wheel or losing precious hours in trial and error. Our community empowers you to resolve issues efficiently.</p>



<p><strong>Knowledge Transfer:</strong> Administrators come and go, but the institutional knowledge you&#8217;ve amassed should persist. Our live technical documentation serves as an invaluable knowledge repository, ensuring a seamless transition when team members shift.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Our Approach</h2>



<p>Our approach is clear, yet exceptionally effective:</p>



<p><strong>Understanding Your Needs:</strong> We work intimately with you to grasp your distinct requirements and challenges.</p>



<p>D<strong>ocumentation Creation:</strong> Our expert community crafts comprehensive, user-friendly technical documents aligned with industry standards.</p>



<p><strong>Regular Updates:</strong> Technical documentation is a living resource. We ensure it remains current and reflects any changes in standard processes or systems.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Training</h2>



<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Get our training &#8211; REFINE AND ELEVATE YOUR ONLINE BUSINESS NOW, YES, YOURS! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<p>Do your systems feel overly complex, burdened by unnecessary layers of complication?</p>



<p>Are you grappling with an excess of unnecessary processing?</p>



<p>Our community stands as a meticulously curated library designed to empower businesses in their progression and scaling journey.</p>



<p>We&#8217;ve crafted this community to support administrators facing development challenges, showing them the way to craft niche software applications with a touch of practice and expert guidance.</p>



<p>We wholeheartedly believe that YOU can revolutionize your business, achieving the success you know you&#8217;re capable of.</p>



<p>No more stress, no more confusion; this community serves as a dedicated resource to alleviate your worries about:</p>



<ul>
<li>Concepting</li>



<li>Wireframing</li>



<li>Testing</li>



<li>Programming</li>



<li>Social Engagement</li>



<li>Emails</li>
</ul>



<p>Is it as easy as it sounds?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Unlock the Potential</h2>



<p>It&#8217;s time to unlock the full potential of your administrative operations. Bid farewell to inefficiencies, confusion, and wasted time. Embrace the power of technical documentation and watch your team flourish.</p>



<p>Join us today and take the first step towards streamlined, efficient administration. Our documented experience and community will equip you with the mastery of software development, establishing you as the authority in your field.</p>



<p>Don&#8217;t hesitate; the future of efficient administration is just a click away.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">What sets us apart?</h2>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-text-align-center">Our Unique Value Proposition.</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading has-text-align-center has-headline-small-font-size">Our Vision: To resolve your business challenges.</h3>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading has-text-align-center has-headline-small-font-size">Our Mission: To fortify the service industry.</h3>



<hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity is-style-dots"/>



<p><strong>Question</strong>: What keeps you up at night?</p>



<p><strong>Insight</strong>: The health and maturity of your business and partner relationships.</p>



<p><strong>Question</strong>: Is there an alternative that provides a solution to your situation?</p>



<p><strong>Insight</strong>: Our community crafts software and promotes services for businesses effectively, offering companies cost-effective, high-quality empowerment without the need to sift through questionable, ineffective offerings. You can depend on us.</p>



<p><strong>Our niche</strong>: Empowering administrators to enhance efficiency through specifically developed software and serve more customers through smart acquisition methods.</p>



<p><span style="text-transform:uppercase"><strong>The Results</strong></span>: Every problem we solve for our clients takes us one step closer to fulfilling our mission. It&#8217;s no longer just about the money. Every member in our community knows that their work is meaningful, and the harder they strive, the more people enjoy profound, restful, and dramatically improved sleep. We&#8217;re inspired by vision, passion, determination, and the niche we adore, and we get to change the world, one small business at a time.</p>



<p>If our vision resonates with you…</p>



<p>Then contact us immediately!</p>



<p><strong>I&#8217;ll leave you with some food for thought</strong>.</p>



<p style="font-size:1.7em"><strong><em>Systems thinking!</em></strong></p>



<p>Evaluate choices through these principles:</p>



<p><strong>Leverage</strong> (a machine… engine): from high/low input to high/low output<br><strong>Duration</strong>: half-life/decay-rate<br><strong>Fallibility</strong>: second-order consequences/side-effects (impurity)/leakage<br><strong>Compounding</strong>: presence of feedback/byproduct, preferably positive, affecting scale and reusability</p>



<p><br><em>High-return</em> samples:</p>



<ul>
<li>Capital/asset allocation</li>



<li>Incentive structures</li>



<li>Restructuring</li>



<li>Long-term partnerships</li>



<li>Radical innovation</li>
</ul>



<p><br>Low-return samples:</p>



<ul>
<li>Non-consistent, micro-managed, spontaneous actions</li>



<li>Daily meals</li>



<li>Wardrobe choices</li>
</ul>



<p>P.S. Did I mention my fondness for coding Redux.js apps? And that I also love Sublime Text! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/270c-1f3fb.png" alt="✌🏻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/introduction/">Introduction</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://seandinwiddie.com/community/">Sean Dinwiddie</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://seandinwiddie.com/community/introduction/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
